http://www.eliters.com/games/main/privacy.asp

ABOUT US
ProfileOrganization StructureTestimonialsPrivacy PolicyTerms of Service
MY TICKETS
Eliters is a Fun and Family League, No Gambling, Betting, or Wagering.Eliters serves ads on its site in accordance with our Privacy Policy. Using our site means that you acknowledge acceptance of this policy.
12/11/2020 -
00:34  EST
Privacy Policy
Eliters.com is a part of Nasser, Ghattas & Co. - Computer Services Division.
At Eliters.com we recognize that privacy is important. This Policy applies to all
the products and services offered by Eliters.com and other Nasser, Ghattas & Co. web sites.
If you have any questions about this Policy, please feel free to Contact
Us.
Information we collect and how we use it:
We offer several services that do not require you to register for an account or
provide any personal information to us, such as Eliters.com Search. In order to
provide all our services, we may collect the following types of information:
Information you provide: When
you sign up for an Account or other service that requires registration, we ask
you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account
password).
Eliters.com cookies: When
you visit Eliters.com, we send one or more cookies (a small file containing a
string of characters) to your computer that uniquely identifies your web
browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing
user preferences and tracking user trends, such as how people search. Most
web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your
browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent.
However, some features and services at Eliters.com may not function properly
if your browser's cookies are disabled.
Web log information: When
you use Eliters.com services, our servers automatically record information
that your web browser sends whenever you visit a web site. These server logs
may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (IP)
address, browser type, browser language, browser plug-ins, the date and time
of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your
browser.
User communications: When
you send email or other communication to Eliters.com, we may retain those
communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests
and improve our services.
Affiliated web sites: We
offer some of our services in connection with other web sites. Personal
information that you provide to those web sites may be sent to Eliters.com in
order to deliver the service. We process such information in accordance with
this Policy. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and
we encourage you to read their privacy policies. Affiliated web sites
include payment processing companies; such as PayPal and WorldPay; and they
request credit card or other payment account information which they maintain
in encrypted form on secure servers; we have no access to such Credit
Card information.
Web links: Eliters.com
may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these
links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of
our search services and web site content.
Other web sites: This
Privacy Policy applies to web sites and services that are owned and operated
by Nasser, Ghattas & Co.. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as search
results or links from within our various services. These other sites may
place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or
solicit personal information from you.
Eliters.com only processes personal information for the purposes described in the
applicable Privacy Policy and/or privacy notice for specific services. In
addition to the above, such purposes include:
Providing our products and services to users,
including the display of customized content and advertising.
Auditing, research and analysis in order to
maintain, protect and improve our services.
Ensuring the technical functioning of our web
site and the services it provides.
Contacting you when needed especially for news, membership maturity,
events announcements, arrange matches with other members, and other notices.
Developing new services.
Choices for personal information
When you sign up for a particular service that requires registration, we ask you
to provide personal information. If we use this information in a manner
different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your
consent prior to such use.
If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those
described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, we will offer
you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those
other purposes. We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes
other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service
notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent.
You can decline to submit personal information to any of our services, in which
case Eliters.com may not be able to provide those services to you.
Information sharing
Eliters.com only shares personal information with other companies or individuals
outside of Eliters.com and Nasser, Ghattas & Co. in the following limited circumstances:
We have your consent. We require opt-in consent
for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.
We provide such information to our sister
companies, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for
the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require
that these parties agree to process such information based on our
instructions and in compliance with this Policy and any other appropriate
confidentiality and security measures.
We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal
information, such as the number of users who searched for a particular term, for
example, or how many users clicked on a particular advertisement. Such
information does not identify you individually.
However, these third parties may place and read cookies on your browser, or may
use web beacons to collect information, in the course of displaying certain
parts of Eliters.com pages.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit Eliters.com.
These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email
address or telephone number) about your visits to this website and to other web
sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to
you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your
choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click
here.
Google, as a third party advertising vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our
website. In this respect, please note the following:
Google's use of the DoubleClick
DART cookie enables it to
serve ads to our website users based on their visit to our website and other
websites on the Internet.
You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie
by visiting the Google
ad and content network privacy policy.
Information security
We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to
or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include
internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and
security measures.
We restrict access to personal information to Nasser, Ghattas & Co. employees, contractors and
agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve
our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may
be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if
they fail to meet these obligations.
Data integrity
Eliters.com processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was
collected and in accordance with this Policy. We review our data collection,
storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and
process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We
take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is
accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct
their personal information whenever necessary.
Enforcement
Eliters.com regularly reviews its compliance with this Policy. Please feel free
to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Policy or our treatment of
personal information by contacting
us.
Changes to this policy
Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not
reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent, and we
expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Policy
changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more
prominent notice.
Home -
About Us -
TOS -
Contact Us -
Privacy -
Site Map -
Help
Tell a Friend -
Web Development Emox
Disclaimer: Eliters is a fun, friendly, and family tournament-based online League. Eliters Members can play online tournaments in many games of skill available on Free Play Sites on the Internet. Eliters is a non-gambling skill-based competition; No Gambling, Betting, or Wagering; Eliters is Free to all; you can register, participate in tournaments, and win points to continue playing forever completely Free.
